don't worry we're back back we're back
some some some Skokie's were mad that
you didn't get to come to the gas
station with us it was actually really
cool
we've met a nice guy he traveled all
around the country because it was in the
army to freestyle on my Instagram they
might be they might be remember
everybody might be a potential , AI
customer so in the interest of new
corporate communication we went back to
the school to talk to the fourth and
fifth graders genders we didn't we
didn't buy you a Slurpee he was asking
everyone so but we did buy water Joe we
did buy water Joe heck don't you we
should really just what if we really
figured out how to monetize our
awareness to know like I really think we
could easily do this next year we have
to figure out how to get real corporate
sponsorship yeah we could we're shilling
to thousands of dedications this is like
better than like Instagram models right
people who are like in our demographic
we'll just have to set up sponsorship
deals we're gonna get the next one
sponsored but this year it wasn't
sponsored there's a good lesson it was a
good lesson but but that's why the title
of this periscope is what it is yeah
because without your continued support
come a does not continue just like Jimmy
Wales and Wikipedia
without Jimmy Wales Wikipedia without
your donations Wikipedia does coffee for
two dollars stuff together we're really
trying to save money and we talked about
me not eating food but two dollars I
thought we could splurge
two bucks I got a cinnamon sugar North
it looks like nine no way we have 55
drivers someone says the Internet's
crappy any maybe we're holding it wrong
I'm blocking antenna gate all over it
all over the place to hold cell phones
people don't know that's what young
they're mounted like this ya know I'm
sorry when you bring you guys at the gas
station but like it would've been like
your meeting like 60 people here it's
all over well you know Bose like YouTube
stars just like walk around La in life
to know I don't know how they do that
we really want to be on your show to
reach all of your know tonight that
sucks I don't know I don't like like his
older stuff was okay but I feel that
he's just become so corporatized
oh he's so corporate realizing and he's
like getting depressed about it
I mean he's really depressed about yeah
that's that's like weed right like
videos were so good everybody should be
depressed about becoming corporatized
which is like then what are you what are
your values right that's a question that
you really have to ask you watch these
videos once and I was like we're not
they spend an hour air time chillin 4kz
nights guys if anyone's out there anyone
out there there's trouble packing their
bags you got to get some packing packing
cubes change if you're on a long trip
you need packing cubes you need your
your socks and underwear separate from
your shirts you
your warm clothes and one one small cute
for this trip love packing - sorry I'm
sorry - I'm just worried he's gonna
watch this I mean I don't think that
highly of ourselves but I'm just saying
like this is an interview to potential
sponsors next year we're gonna show
Kevin oh you're right this is how good
we are chilling okay I want you to
everybody to look two days ago we shield
for good point - now Bitcoin caches on
coinbase Agito we didn't know by the way
we did not know I'm not saying that
correlation and causation are the same
thing but I'm just saying if we show for
you good things happen to you yep make
$60 today so far maybe even more
but guys what we're really shilling for
here is kind of the eye that's who we
are
this car is driving himself right now
with hardware from the shop at shop
Comic Con today I also believe it or not
these periscopes are not scripted would
anyone believe they've worse these are
not pre-recorded virtually Chris Shawn
you know they actually are pre-recorded
we predicted you were going to say that
Bachman is telling you to eat more
protein George what you'll absorb dude
when are they gonna make water they're
gonna make war with dawn
be more protein emerging last night yeah
what's up it still we went to this place
old Chicago we have no idea why lovely
good pizza good service kind people I
think it deserves like a four point one
yeah hey how much you want to bet their
sales I can go up we shelling we don't
even know it
we're just shelled by the way sweets
sweets have been nice Sui tea yes you
are do three beds I didn't even know
these things existed man sweet something
sweets up and great considering we have
no money we have to cut back so we're
sleeping in the wrap for tonight yeah
we're sleeping with sleeping in the rav4
in La Crosse Wisconsin
now unless unless people buy things
right now
if come a I employee is the place to
sleep yeah that'd be nice yeah i'm
pardon the interruption this upcoming
fridge is brought to you by so we can
reach hill will Rochelle bar brought you
by the EON
this is the common yard right here yeah
just like this one you can have your
very own Aeon at home this e on Odie
it's the build quality of this you
actually know it's really good but don't
you want black screws in there no no
black screws only for internal yawns Oh
Kevin is asking when you're gonna drop
it on the track
I know I really I want to do something
I'm gonna work on it when I get home
like I'm not even kidding like if you
guys listen to 5:00 a.m. in Silicon
Valley I put some real effort yeah I try
to put effort into life like that track
and and the one I have on Spotify is
called the cold war because Russia is
cold or maybe the only tracks that I
really put effort into the other ones I
kind of do it a day I want to do I want
to do a good one reflect on your past
week
reflect my last year to be honest yeah
guys I know like every music musician
says this right and you can hear this
and everybody all the fans are like oh
yeah come on man that's not true you're
so cool all right but says what you know
to her songs oh yeah being on tour is
this kind of miserable
just here you have to just go go you're
going shout out to the small bands that
go on tour like Sam there is something
so like romantic and honest about that
life yeah that I worry that like this
sort of wasn't like here we worried
billion OTO Toyota George you like
Arby's we're gonna get you Sandra
Clemens why is it why is George always
in the driver's seat because only I
Drive I drove for an hour this is
originally gonna be my road trip you
guys George how would you the periscope
George how would you have done this I
would you've done the store anything
took charge of selling seven things for
our meals it's been extravagantly on
this tour
not really you guys we believe our
generous $100 dinners for three people
yeah I don't know if that's extravagant
no dis engagements the store someone's
asking we're gonna we're gonna make a
blog post about are you how many dis
engagements what percentage we really
are really I would like I mean I would
have conglomerate all the video of
America I would rating the video yeah
yeah well we'll try to do something but
to be honest it depends how many sales
we get if we can get to ten thousand
dollars in sales
today today that's it gets it over 1,600
right now if we can get that up to ten
thousand today we will write you guys
the most beautiful blog post you've ever
seen we'll really go over this maybe
let's make it more achievable 7,000
7,000 7,000 coming today I shopped at
comedy I if we can sell seven thousand
dollars worth of worth of merch
like you want to join a check and see
Oh tectum saying we should ask yuan for
some of his hat money yeah you won guys
I feel bad
yuan broke too Ilan is so broke like
trying to make those model threes like
the investors test is like the highest
most shorted stock on the market so why
I think a lot of you'll get them on
you'll get them on Twitter there's
people who are really emotional that's
short and Tesla I'm like oh my god
you're gonna lose money and you know
what the worst part is you're gonna lose
money and you're not going to be able to
admit you were wrong right it's like the
people with Bitcoin holy tomorrow
around 1820 $87,000 tell your friends
we're having a come AI shopping drive
today you get us up to $7,000 we lowered
it from 10 we made it fair it's not
being lowered again only seven seven
thousand dollars we will put together
the blip the best blog post from this
trip showing disengagement showing when
we were engaged with maps with
everything with everything to go the
collaboration yeah yeah we could yeah
you guys joined us for this road trip
but you will join us do it you'll really
like like data if you like facts and
data with your 7,000 dollars we will be
able to afford a bit of engineering time
to make this happen but we don't get a
seven thousand dollars by the time we
get to La Crosse the cross if we get to
seven thousand before we get to the
cross blog post if we don't know blog
post yet you want to me so sometimes
corporations reach out to work with me
and I basically do this I'm like okay
tell me exactly what you want what
you're willing to pay for it and wire me
ten percent as a down payment by this
date
and they'll do it we'll go back and
forth with
right and then the date goes by and then
they still want to talk about more
I'm like guys now you have to
send me the thing by that date there's
nothing to talk about right like that's
just how it is
um so that's how it's gonna be with the
blog post but if we do get a 7000 it'll
be posted out there yeah RVs are just me
to show Fred a bit more and say thank
you Arby's actually gave over yeah and
asked opieop they post this on the
budget for a yeah
don't show anyone's personal mission
we're not gonna let call your name on
anything unless you call yourself out on
periscope and we're happy to shout you
out
now keep those waters off let's see if
we can get to $7,000 $7,500 ating we
make the safe decision of continuing to
steer and Bernie could not just to be
people a disengagement as an actual
safety not being safety vanilla gorilla
is upset you teased about the people
were upset that we didn't bring him into
the guys I'm just letting people down
today you know I didn't let down though
this beta is the class of fourth graders
and fifth graders I was almost like
she's basically attitude before the
fifth graders they wanted demos and
doing demos you guys okay so now
allegedly I'm distracted I'm not don't
worry
well we're getting we're gonna see what
happens
so that's the bar you can see there's
only a tiny little bit left
we should start losing that's what
happens but now if I touch the wheel we
reached out to Panda Express on Twitter
to be the exclusive in real life
distributor how many I panda they
haven't gotten back right next to your
sugar chicken sugar chicken and sugar
chicken why why people with uncompelled
cars should buy a panda panda lets you
collect more data on your car let's
reverse engineer your car see sensors
like door sensors individual wheels
RPMs be anything you wanna know about
your car you can get with a panda and it
is also except with our - it is also the
first step to make it there card on it
so you'll need a panda to get into your
car find out what's going on at Niko
compiling
as all about Troy's cars at mama
I don't know man we really look at the
users don't we meet Alex Roy with this
live stream tell we're talking about
you're talking about
ya know big eyes like I really I don't
think they realize the top of the life
they have lost which is on them switch
the switch easy I think a lot of people
don't realize that we really are in a
self-driving car right now yeah they
don't realize they don't get it no I
mean I think the leg like they're like
cool is the wood what is this right yeah
you were really confused like someone
was like what did I just some people are
scared when they hit with a stone you
know and this of course plug into
giraffes giraffe
kold-draft says along that quick draft
which came first
Connor the Toyota real nice your
different girl said yes that Toyota's
rap is the highest quality print I've
seen I don't get why it's something
about the design it just it is it is
good yeah yeah we're 3d print all of
these in our basements
so is asking kidneys which leads in
self-driving planes are kind of gimmicky
what I've heard from actually Tesla
Motors have have that they're like it's
crystal but like I pressed the blinker
and I wait for it to change lanes put on
the blinker I'm not even disengaging
notice I'm putting on the blinker
research the health bar go like this put
yourself into the lane and let it cop
with me to go just to the lane change
right in it's like it's faster than the
system would do it it's just like I've
heard like people are frustrated by the
tesla system right yeah gonna change his
legs back here like her dad you guys
someone at the car dealership was
telling me that back in the 70s to use
to do like the drive from Kansas a time
for all the time if he was so 40 to take
a broomstick and just shove it on the
gas pedal and keep it at like 65 70
that was his another cruise yeah really
he was like Tibet I didn't think that a
person is like you think is asking when
do you guys think you'll reach level 3
let me do real question is where we're
gonna reach the cross that's what we
have to be at $7,000 which day is on
sale
we don't have any right now because
there's no exclusive guys let me tell
you something
hoodies are all the monopolies like
they're really you know a processing
power doubles every 18 months putting
price doubles every three months though
he's Leslie pretty kind of double the
price by omission to read the comments
on the comment I buddy at shop doc mama
da di when we tell you about choice
everybody out there right now even if
they're not looking to buy something
just go in a shop comment videos come
come come into our store can't fix ask
you about our deaf men our definite just
like what it is how it works
it's at home it's on your with other
kids I'm driving the car you can't buy
it you can't buy
it's definitely takes in a picture and
tells you how far away is I'll tell
you guys a little bit about it the
architecture kind of looks like a unit
architecture it was trained mostly on
that that thought oh you can get easy
ground truth depth on that yeah I mean
stuff off we're working on supervisor
right depth you know this car has two
cameras right you see the tail well it
only looks like one to you because you
only exist at one moment in time but if
you look at two moments in time you have
one camera in each moment actually
different places
someone's asking so Shepard plus now is
FC double W for vehicles without radar
no now without radar now but if your
vehicle has radar they are connected to
it it doesn't need open pilot support it
just needs a radar yeah so like all the
Honda's in all the Toyotas will work
with ship applause MCW see this scenario
here he's slowing down so where does it
keep going
I know he's not after all it didn't yeah
people here are trying but not like
California drivers
but they do make things like see right
yeah yeah hold it so it's like I'm just
asking about memory issues forgetting is
going to be a problem in depth Matt's
forgetting is gonna be more of a problem
as our driving models start to get more
sophisticated and we have more educates
like behavior Lauren our self-driving
I don't have a reddit account we have
one at the top most of our self-driving
we are literally in a self-driving car
right now yeah check something tectum is
asking when you buy any on you can
install open pilot yeah so if you go to
github.com so I'm coming pilot
[Music]
download it put it on your ear
virtually Chris has a video out there
how to do this okay there we have to be
clear though there's no official support
for that after you modify again we do
not officially sell anything that drives
cars would you not officially support
any hardware or consumer products the
drive cars I'm so you are on your own
that is kind of a dozen cam Vick the EON
does not have a rate we're using the
cars built-in radar
lianna's one forward facing camera the
new did not have a radar though the PIO
is pretty much the same
capabilities as in beyond beyond has a
better thermal solution about 15 watts
five shitty 37 so you can do seven I
guess but we have like thermal paste
with a custom sink on the EON that's
what let's it 0.4 draws more power which
was about 10 watts instead of seven
Wow this cars got that circle dough not
been in this chip
thanks to Ricardo Andy home crew doing a
great job
yeah I got you to go okay yeah no
problem
what's the car rav4 who's that people
taking my chance
that's terribly annoying yeah you got
you got sailor for beeps you know it's a
level two system new models yeah they're
coming something soon team up now we're
actually this sort of model with like
the two lanes in the path in the lead
car this is the last version of the
bottle that's ever going to be like that
um the new models are a new architecture
we're working yo hold on reven just said
Ricardo is time for my favorite comment
and I'm a little worried who he's tied
with so private if you don't mind the
Employee of the Year in 2017 went a
little kind of wanted to go there how do
you get to take it
how's this upper angle people like this
that uppers
the selfie angle
so here's the thing when up for Evan
instead I'm pretty awesome virtually
Chris asking what the new architecture
will look like so it's going to just
directly predict the path it's going to
like the path is going to be a direct
output of the model no more lanes see
that's the thing people like all to own
bullet hit the rumble strips once the
other thing too is like he probably does
have a cruise control set it like 70 or
something yeah but his 70 is not a real
70 it's actually 68 300 a 70-year so
Harmar 70 is a true 7
the car says it's 72
what do you guys do for jobs leave jobs
hey jobs the AI is taking all the jobs I
mean our job is to put our jobs out
but we're all computer real French so
that's well well we'll see if we'd be
real with you now we can tell will be
real rich artist order squamata guy
right now just touch the wheel tracks
asking you different lands to add more
cameras yeah that's another oh we wanted
like we really need a hammer so religion
is disengagement tracking system so when
we do feel limited by our single camera
scenarios where this is the physical or
another camera
we are very deliberate motivations for
partner system yeah Harbor cross some
money hardware has recurring expense
software only has not requiring expense
to always want to do something you know
if you can in software that's like
featuring obviously this bog Joe is
nothing sir Buxton hardware but you
don't know workaround Hardware bugs some
software but if you can replace more or
more expensive hardware with software
you should always do this
this is why cameras are gonna be lighter
but I mean I've talked to Ricardo right
now I think that this open pilot is
ready to release to the public so we're
going to push it probably tonight to
devel you guys can start checking out
0.4 with all of its goodness
a little bit of retuning we've been
we've been constantly iterating on this
as we go this things i complain about so
by the time you buy stuff right now
you'll have the hardware ready to go
when the software launches
how exciting they got the phone how many
spell bees 4828 over losing people yeah
we drop this up this was ago might be
because we have bad signal I was
advancing
that's fine ship it out man
what
we found a bug the waves crashing
the bug is fixed we just have to think
about how to actually ship
you know I don't think so I think that's
why I think we ship without it that bug
would be fixed to like actually soon not
even sweetie
the gorillas got his new rear room here
nice pretty nice got push the do doesn't
work
I think we might have a bunch of
improvements of sugar plus as well we
head above these interface places
crashing I'm not sure exactly as the bug
was but uh it's fixed now it's a little
tight
yeah
you loosen which it should be a little
tight yeah yeah just taking my time
taking my ass better off and they're
normal things you would do when you're
driving without a baby what we should do
is we should increase them to time out
there now the issue is we want to give
people time to get out of there ya know
it's important so we disengage the
system if you're Mun Clifton the driver
seat belt obviously not the other seat
belts or if you open the door because
this is not
there's just good general safety fixed
have a good cruise control system should
have until drinks that blue Jake Jake
subclass honor guard might go where you
try maybe missing overpass yeah we got
forty force Kofi's
people are people who drop all right all
right you know what
always always pull a Kurt Cobain you're
ahead wait a second what Alex - just
super hard at us I don't even know that
was a thing oh my god slick tint in
there now that I love you so logic not
intermarry how do you super hard Alex
Roy says don't leave us is Alice right
here now what she was here all right all
right I'll always heal with Tim Clemons
says Alex Roy says don't leave us so I
don't know Alex Roy show yourself yeah
actually sure some would give him a
little more time let's see if we back up
over 50 45 1957 thank you five things we
really want to sell some beyond you know
about a hoodie they said there's never a
better time to buy beyond than right now
because the ship right now
you're ordering Ilan like next week
little ship next year good say if you
wanted me on right now it'll ship
tomorrow
yeah all right oh my god 49 are they
coming back all right we can we can hang
out for a bit more did you scope he's
like the one last night nothing nowhere
yeah panda needs to be out of safety
mode
that's correct impatient no not out of
safety what so pandas have multiple
safety the default safety mode is the
Panda doesn't allow anything to be sent
and this is the mode used by Schaefer
PLAs and shiver shiver can now switch in
a dual mode which only allows things to
be sent then there is an all-access
safety mode which Oakland pilot never
uses the ones that open pilot uses at a
car specific one so there's one for
Honda is one for Toyota all of this code
is open source in the Panda repo
so github common type and we have the
different safety profiles for the
different cars and they enforce things
like torque limits they enforce things
like you know if you press any pedals it
disengages all of those kind of things
all right I think we're leaving here you
know what we should schedule when the
next one is yes you think more people
show up well I think yeah so give gift
of Skokie's that are out there time to
promote it again yeah well we can like
post it on our self-driving cars say
maybe this is the last periscope with a
self-driving car to talk about our
$7,000 goal which we were actually two
sevenths of the way to yeah at the
beginning of this one we were only at
like 1200 we made $800 since disco me
that's almost as much as we made showing
for pick my cash AJ lesson go go to get
up and check out what language the code
is written in Python Python and C I bet
it's eight but check it out frozen by
the way pythons driving this car oh no
what if the GC runs fine doorbell I'll
check
all right what time is the next four
times now
- you 39 339 alright 5 p.m.
yep 5 p.m. we will be back on the
periscope yep
tell your friends gonna really show off
the self-driving car I think 5 p.m. tide
is a good time to bring in some new
people
hi guys oh wait I feel what I don't know
Central Time yeah I don't even know it's
it's a time okay it's an hour and 20
minutes 20 minutes from central Central
Standard Time is that ready standard
time that's like 3 p.m. Pacific time 6
p.m. Eastern and don't live in America I
don't know what just how you tell your
friend God Joe I know your own times
right